Guide to the Fred Ross papers M0812
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series B. Subject Files (7 linear feet)
  - Subseries: Press Clippings
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1972 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- Stockton (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Harper's, June 1965 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Individualist [n.d.] (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - The Nation, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Playboy, March 1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Ramparts, July 1966 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Ramparts, August 1966 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Ramparts, Aug.-Sept. 1973 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Luis Valdez, "Tribute. Dolores Huerta," 1990 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Articles about Ross (Box 15 (legal), Folder 1)
    - La Raza (Los Angeles), 1979 (Box 15 (legal), Folder 2)
    - La Verdad (San Diego, CA), 1969 (Box 15 (legal), Folder 3)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1974 (Box 15 (legal), Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1960's (Box 15 (legal), Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1970's (Box 15 (legal), Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings-- Hanford, CA, 1955 (Box 15 (legal), Folder 7)
    - The Sunday Times Magazine, 1970 (Box 15 (legal), Folder 8)
  - Subseries: Training Materials
    - Boycott Campaigns-- Perelli-Minetti (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Boycotters Handbook (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Buidling the Winning Boycott (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Community Organizing (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Election Organizing Manual, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Farm Workers..." (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Feinstein training session, re-election campaign for mayor of San Francisco, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Field Office House Meeting Outline (Florida) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - The First House Meeting (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - John Gardner, An Organizer's Training Manual (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "History of the Farm Worker Movement as told by Fred Ross, Sr....1974" (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - House meeting and personal visit outlines (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - House meeting notes (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - House meeting notes (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - House meeting originals (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - House meeting rap (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - House meeting (Spanish-language), Florida (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - House meeting training, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Eliseo Medina, "Setting up a boycott" (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Organizing and recruitment (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Outline Action Program - Boycott, mid-1970's (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Outline House Meeting - Farm Workers (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Outline House Meeting/ NY and NJ, mid-1970's (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "People Power Must Be Invisible..." (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - P.V. (English-language), Florida (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Ranch Committees Organizing (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - "Recruitment: Fred Ross" (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Revised Spanish-language packet (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Ross Housemeeting Method (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Ross on Camp Program (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Survival Institute Training, Los Angeles, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Toronto Boycott Staff, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Training-- Alameda, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Training--Feinstein Campaign, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Training-- Guadalupe, Arizona, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Training-- "Organizer Training. Post-Mortems of the First...1976" (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Training-- "Summary House Meeting and P.V. Outline," August 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Training-- Texas, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Training-- Misc. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Training Format (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Training Lessons-- Breaking Into the Community (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Training Lessons-- Calling, Chairs, Finding People (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Training Lessons-- Door Openers (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Training Lessons-- The Fallacy of Helping (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Training Lessons-- Getting Yourself Organized (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Training Lessons-- The Initial Phone Call (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Training Lessons-- Learning People's Names (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Training Lessons-- Learnings (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Training Lessons-- Leaving Messages (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Training Lessons-- Licking Fear (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Training Lessons-- Making a Schedule (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Training Lessons-- Mass Meeting (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Training Lessons-- Peer Pressure (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Training Lessons-- Philosophy of Blaming Others (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Training Lessons-- The Phone Call (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Training Lessons-- The Phone Call (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Training Lessons-- P.V.'s (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Training Lessons-- Religious Leaders (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Training Lessons-- Reminder Call (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Training Lessons-- The Reminder Call (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Training Lessons-- Students' Notes/ Manual/ Gardner (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Training Lessons-- "They Are Not Prepared - You Are" (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Training Lessons-- The "Whats" and the "Hows" (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Training Lessons-- Who Are They - The Ones You Organize (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Training Materials (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Training Materials (English-language) (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Training Materials (English-language) (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Training Materials (Spanish-language) (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Training Materials (Spanish-language) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Training Materials-- Misc. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Training Notes, Feb. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Larry Tramutt, Farm Workers (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - UFW-- Brooklyn Training, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Workshop with Fred Ross, La Paz, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Boycott Campaigns-- DiGiorgio (Box 18 (legal), Folder 1)
    - Boycott Campaigns-- Gallo (Box 18 (legal), Folder 2)
    - Building the Winning Boycott (Box 18 (legal), Folder 3)
    - Fort Worth Training Session [n.d.] (Box 18 (legal), Folder 4)
    - Giumarra (Box 18 (legal), Folder 5)
    - House Meeting Outlines (Box 18 (legal), Folder 6)
    - LA Training, 1974 (Box 18 (legal), Folder 7)
    - Organizing-- Ranch Committees (Box 18 (legal), Folder 8)
    - Training for Survival (Box 18 (legal), Folder 9)
    - Training Lessons-- Omitting the 1 Step (Box 18 (legal), Folder 10)
    - Training Lessons-- Perception/ Blaming Others (Box 18 (legal), Folder 11)
- Series C. Manuscripts (3 linear feet)
  These boxes hold Ross' writings, largely unpublished (with one or two exceptions). The manuscripts are mostly autobiographical. He often wrote of himself in the third person or as "you" in an interior dialogue putting the reader in Ross's place. His writings include extensive portraits of Cesar Chavez and Dolores Huerta (see "Woman in Motion").
  One of the original boxes in the collection bore the note that "this box contains the papers Fred worked and reworked in the 1990's-they are mostly as he left them. We can't really discern what he truly wanted as final drafts -he reworked his writings for decades." This is true of the entire Manuscript Series. Because Ross' manuscripts were work in progress and often undated, it can be difficult to discern the order in which drafts were written. Moreover, some manuscripts have missing pages that were presumably taken out as Ross worked to revise his writings, or the pages were lost in the course of his many moves. Due to the number of manuscripts, any missing pages are not noted in the guide.
  The manuscript titles listed in the guide reflect the title listed on the document itself, but sometimes drafts of the same story carried different titles. Another complication is that Ross often wrote in a style that used many short chapters or frequent subheadings, so that every few pages brings a new title and it is not clear what the title of the whole manuscript was. In this case, only the title given on the first page is listed. Finally, there are numerous untitled manuscripts listed in the guide. In most cases these are missing the first few pages; often the untitled manuscripts are versions of documents that have titles, but the processor has left this decision to the judgement of the individual researcher.
  - "Autobiographical." "Workbook of a Wayfaring Organizer" (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Axioms (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Axioms (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Bell Town Unity League" (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Beginnings, L.A. CSO" (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Bloody Xmas" (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Bob Hardie" (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Book Drafts (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Book Drafts, Beginning (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Book Outline (Bell Town and Casa Blanca) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Book Proposal, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Book/ Santa Ana (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Boyle Hts. - L.A. CSO," "Drop Back" (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "Casa Blanca" (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "Cesar Resigns from CSO" (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "Cesar Tries His Wings." Part II of the Chronicle of Cesar Chavez (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - "Cesar Tries Wings" (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - "Community Organization in Mexican American Colonies...1946-47" (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Conquering Goliath (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Conquering Goliath, Foreword (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "Conversion - Challenge" (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "CSO-- First Membership Meeting" (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "Dangling Loose Ends" (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Delano (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Dolores Huerta. Woman in Motion (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "Draft-- LA CSO Henry Nava House Meeting" (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Draft Ross wrote for Carey McWilliams (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "The First House Meeting" (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "Fred Ross, David and Goliath," "The Helstein Plan" (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "Get Out If You Can" (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "Get Out If You Can" (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Get Out If You Can (1953) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "Give It A Go" (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "Guadalupe" (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - "LA River" (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - "The Last Round/ Tony Rios/ Bloody Xmas" (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - "Lincoln Heights" (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript about Chavez (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript about LULAC (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript about LULAC (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "Mario Andretti" (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Mexican Americans on the March" (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "The Next Night" (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "The Old Man and the Key" (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "Phoney Forbearance" (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Ross-- Feeding My Head" (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Ross-- How started working with Farm Workers" (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Ross-- Influences" (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Ross-- Worrying and Reflecting" (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Rudy Aroused" (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "Ruth Tuck" (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "The Saga of Sal Si Puedes" (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "The Saga of Sal Si Puedes" (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "San Bernardino. Ruth and Ignacio" (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "SB Book. Cesar Chavez-Fred Ross collaboration" (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Selling Them On You" (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "SRA" (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - "State Relief Administration" (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - "There is a time for sound" (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "Trapp/ Manuel Santa Ana/ Book?" (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - "Woman in Motion" (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "Woman in Motion" (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Woman in Motion" (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 1 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 2 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 3 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 4 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 5 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 6 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Untitled manuscript, part 7 of 7 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Misc. manuscript pages (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - "CC and I in Visalia" (Box 26 (legal), Folder 1)
  - "Saul/ 1st Meeting" (Box 26 (legal), Folder 2)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 26 (legal), Folder 3)
  - Untitled manuscript (Box 26 (legal), Folder 4)
- Series D. Notes (2.5 linear feet)
  This series includes Ross' handwritten notes, notecards, and notebooks. Many of the notes are not clearly labelled or dated. Some appear to be logs of his organizing work, but most are Ross' own sketched notes and outlines for meetings and training sessions. Care has been taken to preserve groups of notes in the order orginally found.
  - Notecards (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Notecards (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Notes (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Notes (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Notes (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Notes (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Notes (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Notes [1974?] (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Notes (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Notes (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Notebooks, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Notebooks, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks [CSO?] (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Workbooks (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Workbooks (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Series E. Photographs (.5 linear feet)
  One box of photographs, mostly from the 1950's, 1960's, and 1970's.
  - Photos (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Photos (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Photos (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Photos-- California/ New England (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Photos-- Cesar Chavez, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Photos-- UFW, early and mid-1970's (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Series F. Audio & Transcripts (444 tapes)
  8 reel to reel tapes were given new numbers in pencil on white stickers in lower left corner. 436 audiocassettes were numbered 1-436 in pencil on white stickers; a few of the cassette cases are empty.
  The audiocassettes are roughly in chronological order. The contents of the tapes' labels have been listed here, although not all are fully labeled. The undated cassettes are grouped together at the end of the series. Where it was obvious that an undated tape belonged with a group of dated tapes, the undated tape was put with them, with the presumed date indicated in brackets. In more dubious cases, the undated tapes were put at the end of the series.
  The tapes are rich in autobiographical materials and in histories of the farm workers' movement. Most of the tapes were made at training sessions for organizers. One particular set, the Wyler-Cohen interviews, is the audiotaped version of a video made to document Ross' life and inspire other organizers.
  - Subseries: Transcripts
    - Central America Peace Education Training Project, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Central America Peace Education Training Project-- Table of Contents for Tapes (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Central America Peace Training Project, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Central America Peace Training (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Notes-- Ohio Tape [n.d.] (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Notes-- Tape on Boston (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Notes-- Tape on Boston (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Notes-- Tape on Brooklyn (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Notes-- Tape on Brooklyn, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Notes-- Tape on Domestic Workers [n.d.] (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Notes-- Tape on Oakland, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Notes-- Tape on Ohio Training, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Notes on Tapes (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Notes on Tapes (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Transcript-- Allliance for Survival, L.A. [1983?] (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Transcript-- AS/ Peace Groups (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Transcript-- Boycott Training, L.A., July 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Transcript-- Brooklyn [n.d.] (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Transcript-- Brooklyn [n.d.] (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Transcript-- Feinstein recall (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Transcript-- Fred Ross, May 8 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Transcript-- Fred Ross and Cesar Chavez, May 7, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Transcript-- Fred Ross and Cesar Chavez, Reel 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Transcript-- Fred Ross and Cesar Chavez, Reel 3 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Transcript-- NSO Meeting, Florida [n.d.] (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Transcript-- ST, FR, CC (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Transcript-- Training, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Transcript-- Training, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Transcript-- Training, Florida UFW, 1974-75 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Transcript-- Training, Oakland, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Transcript Fragment (pp. 11-14) (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Transcript Fragment (pp. 31-34) (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Transcript Fragment (pp. 53-59) (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Subseries: Reel to reel tapes
    - "Cesar - Day after Jones fires [illeg.]" (Box 35 (OS), Folder 1)
    - "Side one - Argument with WPWA-CSO- how Cesar felt. Side 2 - Early contact with R[illegible] and C[illeg.] & to parts of Farm (Box 35 (OS), Folder 2)
    - "Track 2- Cesar - Day after March and Meeting with Hayes. How got [illeg.] work & union. Track 1- Mtg. with Carr [?] - Wages discussed. Cesar's fear abt going to Oxnard. Developments meeting with Hayes wkrs had jobs but only wk'd part of time - halfdays economics of hiring locals vs braceros - Jones [illeg.] with other [illeg.] growers. How Cesar built up [illeg.] against Hayes F.P. [illeg.]. Cesar's fear re going to Oxnard (Box 35 (OS), Folder 3)
    - "Fights for jobs after the carrots [illeg.] with the ladies, stock, irrigation, [illeg.] jobs that don't take [illeg.] people. [Illeg.] "spys" the "sliders" Getting out word the [?] next week were going to [illeg.] this ass or that one - Plans to transfer Emp Pay over to Union - acutal transfer - Union takes over fight vs. [illeg.] Japanese wkrs - Racket tries to get wks to invade private property." (Box 35 (OS), Folder 4)
    - "CSES...Taking wkrs around to Associations....Digression - urges Union to take over Emp Assn....Side 2 - Opposition to Assn's plan to take wkrs to F.P-Ass etc...Cesar takes wks - Mtg with Hayes - Plan for getting complaints..." (Box 35 (OS), Folder 5)
    - "Side 2. Descript of bars, Descript of Garcias place, [illeg.] Story of old man Lopez from Madera...Side one. Argument with Union group re: [illeg.] of jobs vs wages....Descrip of Rachel, Eddie, workers...." (Box 35 (OS), Folder 6)
    - "Dolores" (Box 35 (OS), Folder 7)
    - UFW radio spots (Box 35 (OS), Folder 8)
  - Subseries: Audiocassettes
    - Audiocassettes, numbered 1-72 by Ross
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 1)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 2)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 3)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 4)
      - Phone Discussion. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 5)
      - Phoning. Mona - Friendship [?]/ 198 - Manipulating. Releasing - resisters. Pressure. Preparing for phoning - wrkrs rap (Box 36 (OS), Folder 6)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 7)
      - Role playing phoning. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 8)
      - Role playing phoning. Logistics (Box 36 (OS), Folder 9)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 10)
      - Odds & ends - Prep & protocol of PV. Temptations. Leaving messages. CC - Jan P & Maldonado. Reminder calls - Nag - Prep & Production of PV. Mary M C (Box 36 (OS), Folder 11)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 12)
      - The "never home people." Phone 2 friends. Call at 7 AM-Midnight. Keep eyes open. The PV. Grove WK's house - Casa Blanca. Painting on Wall. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 13)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 14)
      - Prep of PV rap (Box 36 (OS), Folder 15)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 16)
      - Prep of PV (Box 36 (OS), Folder 17)
      - Prep of PV (Box 36 (OS), Folder 18)
      - Prep of PV rap (Box 36 (OS), Folder 19)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 20)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 21)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 22)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 23)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 24)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 25)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 26)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 27)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 28)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 29)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 30)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 31)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 32)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 33)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 34)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 35)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 36)
      - John Adler. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 37)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 38)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 39)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 40)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 41)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 42)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 43)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 44)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 45)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 46)
      - 8/6/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 47)
      - 8/6/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 48)
      - 8/6/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 49)
      - 8/6/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 50)
      - Jaime, Renata, Dan. John Adler HM Rap - incomplete (Box 36 (OS), Folder 51)
      - 8/7/84. Liza, Jaime, Renata, Dan - Post Mortem. 8/7 and 8/8. PV's. Rodrigo (Box 36 (OS), Folder 52)
      - 8/7-8/8/84. Conclusion of John. Kent. PM or PV. Joseph W [?]. John Rodrigo. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 53)
      - Rodrigo PM on PV. (Box 36 (OS), Folder 54)
      - 8/8/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 55)
      - 8/8/84. Cathy and Ned (Box 36 (OS), Folder 56)
      - 8/8/84, 8/9/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 57)
      - 8/9/84. Pressure. Pressure Brouhaha. Lorena quiet HM Post Mortem (Box 36 (OS), Folder 58)
      - 8/9/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 59)